schellgames.com 2019-07-12

# Schell Games' Privacy Policy | Schell Games

Last Revised: July 27, 2018

### Intro­duc­tion

Schell Games respects your privacy and we are committed to protecting it through our compli­ance with this Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy” or this ​“Policy”), our [Terms of Use](https://www.schellgames.com/schell-games-terms-of-use), and our [Cookie Policy](https://www.schellgames.com/schell-games-cookie-policy).

This Privacy Policy describes the types of infor­ma­tion we may collect from you (or that you may provide) when you visit [schellgames.com](http://www.schellgames.com/) (the ​“Website”) and all our related websites, including without limi­ta­tion [jesseschell.com](https://www.jesseschell.com/), [ieytd.com](https://iexpectyoutodie.schellgames.com/), [untilyoufall.com](https://untilyoufall.schellgames.com/), [hololabchampions.com](https://hololabchampions.schellgames.com/), [enemymindgame.com](http://www.enemymindgame.com/), [happyatoms.com](http://www.happyatoms.com/), and [waterbearsgame.com](http://waterbearsgame.com/) (collec­tively, the ​“Websites”), and our practices for collecting, using, main­taining, protecting, and disclosing that infor­ma­tion.

This Policy applies to infor­ma­tion we collect:

  * On our Websites.
  * In email and other elec­tronic messages between you and our team.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to under­stand our policies and practices regarding your infor­ma­tion and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Websites. By accessing or using our Websites, you agree to this Privacy Policy. This policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of our Websites after we make changes is deemed to be accep­tance of those changes, so please check the policy peri­od­i­cally for updates.

Please note our Privacy Policy is part of the [Terms of Use](https://www.schellgames.com/schell-games-terms-of-use) and is incor­po­rated therein by refer­ences.

### Infor­ma­tion We Collect About You and How We Collect It

We collect several types of infor­ma­tion from and about users of our Websites, including infor­ma­tion:

  * by which you may be person­ally iden­ti­fied, such as name, e-mail address, telephone number, address, or any other iden­ti­fier by which you may be contacted online or offline (“personal infor­ma­tion”); and/​or
  * that is about you but indi­vid­u­ally does not identify you, such as ​“aggregate” or ​“anonymized” data.

We collect this infor­ma­tion:

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us; and
  * Auto­mat­i­cally as you navigate through the site. Infor­ma­tion collected auto­mat­i­cally may include infor­ma­tion collected through cookies.

### Infor­ma­tion We Collect Through Automatic Data Collec­tion Tech­nolo­gies

The infor­ma­tion we collect on or through our Websites may include:

  * Infor­ma­tion that is about you but does not indi­vid­u­ally identify you, such as ​“aggregate” or ​“anonymized” data.
  * Infor­ma­tion that you provide by filling in forms on our Websites. This includes infor­ma­tion provided at the time of requesting further infor­ma­tion, signing up to playtest, requesting a media kit, applying for a job, or subscribing to our mailing list. We may also ask you for infor­ma­tion when you report a problem with our Websites.
  * Details of your visits to our Websites, including traffic data, location data, logs and other commu­ni­ca­tion data.
  * Records and copies of your corre­spon­dence (including email addresses), if you contact us.
  * Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research purposes.
  * Your search queries on our Websites.

Again, the infor­ma­tion we collect auto­mat­i­cally is statis­tical (anonymized) data and does not include personal infor­ma­tion, but we may maintain it or associate it with personal infor­ma­tion we collect in other ways. It helps us to improve our Websites and to deliver a better and more person­al­ized service, including by enabling us to:

  * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
  * Store infor­ma­tion about your pref­er­ences, allowing us to customize our Websites according to your indi­vidual interests.
  * Speed up your searches.
  * Recognize you when you return to our Websites.

### The Automatic Data Collec­tion Tech­nolo­gies We Use

We store First Party Tracking Tech­nolo­gies when you visit or access our Websites, when you interact with embedded items on our Websites, and/​or when you interact with Schell Games’ content on Third Party websites (e.g., social media pages). In addition, we authorize certain Third Parties (e.g., our social media and analytics providers) to store Third Party Tracking Tech­nolo­gies.

The tech­nolo­gies we use for this automatic data collec­tion may include Cookies (or browser cookies). A cookie is a small file (piece of text) that’s placed on the hard drive of your computer or mobile device when you visit a webpage. A cookie file is stored in your web browser and allows the Service or a Third Party to recognize you and make your next visit easier and the Service more useful to you. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by acti­vating the appro­priate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Websites. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Websites.

We do not collect personal infor­ma­tion auto­mat­i­cally, but we may tie this infor­ma­tion to personal infor­ma­tion about you that we collect from other sources or you provide to us.

### Third Parties We Authorize To Use Cookies and Other Tracking Tech­nolo­gies.

We authorize the following Third Parties to use the Tracking Tech­nolo­gies which are listed below:

##### GOOGLE ANALYTICS

_Third Party Tracking Tech­nolo­gies: Perfor­mance Tracking Tech­nolo­gies_

Google Analytics uses cookies to collect infor­ma­tion about how people use our Websites. Specif­i­cally, it collects aggregate (anonymous) infor­ma­tion on the number of website visits, certain demo­graphics, likes, interest, user attrition and traffic flow. We use this infor­ma­tion to improve user expe­ri­ence on our Websites.

In addition, this data is collected for remar­keting and retar­geting purposes (i.e., data is used for recom­mending relevant related content). [See Google Analytics Privacy Policy](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245)

##### BANDCAMP

_Third Party Tracking Tech­nolo­gies: Perfor­mance Tracking Tech­nolo­gies_

This tech­nology is used for the purpose of gaining audience insight. Specif­i­cally, Bandcamp uses cookies to collect infor­ma­tion on aggregate sales, downloads, plays and location. [See Bandcamp Privacy Policy](https://bandcamp.com/privacy)

##### FACEBOOK

_Third Party Tracking Tech­nolo­gies: Social Media/​Advertising/​Perfor­mance Tracking Tech­nolo­gies_

Facebook stores cookies which allow the Facebook ​“Like” social sharing func­tion­ality but only if you click on the Facebook ​“Like” button on our Website or log in to the Website using your Facebook account. Facebook also uses cookies to collect aggregate demo­graphics and interests data, which are collected for the purpose of gaining audience insight and adver­tising (i.e., collecting data used for recom­mending relevant related content).

Our pages on Facebook collect aggregate infor­ma­tion on sales, the countries where content is down­loaded, and number of product views. We use this infor­ma­tion to gain audience insight, track product sales/​revenue achieve­ments, and set bench­marks. [See Facebook Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/).  

##### LINKEDIN

_Third Party Tracking Tech­nolo­gies: Social Media/​Advertising Tracking Tech­nolo­gies_

Linkedin collects aggregate demo­graphic infor­ma­tion and data on interests. We use that infor­ma­tion for the purpose of gaining audience insight and adver­tising. [See Linkedin Privacy Policy](https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy).  

##### REDDIT

_Third Party Tracking Tech­nolo­gies: Social Media Tracking Tech­nolo­gies_

This cookie collects aggregate traffic statis­tics for the purpose of audience insight. [See Reddit Privacy Policy](https://www.redditinc.com/policies/privacy-policy).

##### TWITCH

_Third Party Tracking Tech­nolo­gies: Perfor­mance Tracking Tech­nolo­gies_

This tech­nology is used for the purpose of gaining audience insight. Specif­i­cally, Twitch uses cookies to track how people watch videos; including infor­ma­tion on how much of each video is watched and how many times (on average) each video is watched. [See Twitch Privacy Policy](https://www.twitch.tv/p/legal/privacy-policy/).

##### TWITTER

_Third Party Tracking Tech­nolo­gies: Social Media/​Advertising Tracking Tech­nolo­gies_

Twitter stores cookies which allow you tweet about Schell Games content; plus, its cookies collect infor­ma­tion on aggregate demo­graphics and interests for the purpose of adver­tising (i.e., collecting data used for recom­mending relevant related content). [See Twitter Privacy Policy](https://twitter.com/en/privacy).

##### VIMEO

_Third Party Tracking Tech­nolo­gies: Social Media/​Performance Tracking/​Advertising Tracking Tech­nolo­gies_

Vimeo uses cookies to track how people watch videos; including infor­ma­tion on how much of each video is watched and how many videos each visitor views. We use this infor­ma­tion to form expe­ri­ence, perform Craft main­te­nance and track bugs. Plus, we use this data for adver­tising purposes (i.e., recom­mending relevant related content). [See Vimeo Privacy Policy](https://vimeo.com/privacy).

##### YOUTUBE

_Third Party Tracking Tech­nolo­gies: Social Media/​Advertising Tracking Tech­nolo­gies_

Youtube uses cookies to track how people watch videos; including infor­ma­tion on how much of each video is watched and how many videos each visitor views. This data is used to gain audience insight and for adver­tising purposes (i.e., recom­mending relevant related content). [See YouTube Privacy Policy](https://support.google.com/youtube/answer/7671399?p=privacy_guidelines&hl=en&visit_id=1-636657923172714036-2448766762&rd=1).

##### STEAM

_Third Party Tracking Tech­nolo­gies: Perfor­mance Tracking Tech­nolo­gies_

Steam collects aggregate infor­ma­tion on sales, the countries where content is down­loaded, and number of product views. We use this infor­ma­tion to gain audience insight, track product sales/​revenue achieve­ments, and set bench­marks. [See Steam Privacy Policy](https://store.steampowered.com/privacy_agreement/).

##### TUMBLR

_Third Party Tracking Tech­nolo­gies: Social Media Tracking Tech­nolo­gies_

Tumbler uses cookies to collect data on the number of post views, which is used to gain audience insight. [See Tumblr Privacy Policy](https://www.tumblr.com/privacy).

##### MAILCHIMP

_Third Party Tracking Tech­nolo­gies: Perfor­mance Tracking Tech­nolo­gies_

Our newslet­ters are exclu­sively opt-in, and this cookie collects the following infor­ma­tion (which users input): email addresses and names (first and last). We use this infor­ma­tion to send company infor­ma­tion for business devel­op­ment purposes. [See MailChimp Privacy Policy](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/).

##### OCULUS STORE

_Third Party Tracking Tech­nolo­gies: Perfor­mance Tracking Tech­nolo­gies_

This cookie is used (in conjunc­tion with Facebook) to collect infor­ma­tion on aggregate sales data, the country of origin for purchases, and aggregate return frequency data. We use this infor­ma­tion to gain audience insight, track product sales/​revenue achieve­ments, and set bench­marks. [See Oculus Store Privacy Policy](https://www.oculus.com/legal/privacy-policy/).

##### PLAYSTATION STORE

_Third Party Tracking Tech­nolo­gies: Perfor­mance Tracking Tech­nolo­gies_

This cookie collects infor­ma­tion on appli­ca­tion downloads and content curation. We use this infor­ma­tion to gain audience insight, track product sales/​revenue achieve­ments, and set bench­marks. [See PlaySta­tion Store Privacy Policy](https://www.playstation.com/en-us/network/legal/privacy-policy/#scope).

##### GOOGLE PLAY STORE

_Third Party Tracking Tech­nolo­gies: Perfor­mance Tracking Tech­nolo­gies_

This cookie collects infor­ma­tion on appli­ca­tion downloads and content curation. We use this infor­ma­tion to gain audience insight, track product sales/​revenue achieve­ments, and set bench­marks. [See Google Play Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en&gl=us).

##### ITUNES/​APPLE

_Third Party Tracking Tech­nolo­gies: Perfor­mance Tracking Tech­nolo­gies_

This cookie collects infor­ma­tion on appli­ca­tion downloads and content curation. We use this infor­ma­tion to gain audience insight, track product sales/​revenue achieve­ments, and set bench­marks. [See iTunes Connect Privacy Policy](https://developer.apple.com/app-store/review/guidelines/).

##### HUMBLE BUNDLE

_Third Party Tracking Tech­nolo­gies: Perfor­mance Tracking Tech­nolo­gies_

This cookie collects aggregate sales data. We use this infor­ma­tion to gain audience insight, track product sales/​revenue achieve­ments, and set bench­marks. [See Humble Bundle Store Privacy Policy](https://www.humblebundle.com/privacy).

* * *

We reserve the right to authorize addi­tional Third Parties to use Tracking Tech­nolo­gies to collect infor­ma­tion for internal business purposes of expe­ri­ence tuning, main­te­nance and bug tracking in accor­dance with our Privacy Policy.

### How We Use Your Infor­ma­tion

We use infor­ma­tion that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal infor­ma­tion:

  * To present our Websites and their contents to you.
  * To provide you with infor­ma­tion, products, or services that you request from us.
  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
  * To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide though it.
  * To allow you to partic­i­pate in inter­ac­tive features on our Website.
  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the infor­ma­tion.
  * For any other purpose with your consent.

### Disclo­sure of Your Infor­ma­tion

We may disclose aggre­gated infor­ma­tion about our users, and infor­ma­tion that does not identify any indi­vidual, without restric­tion.

We may disclose personal infor­ma­tion that we collect or you provide as described in this Privacy Policy:

  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it. For example, if you give us an email address to use the ​“PLAYTEST SIGNUP” feature of our Website, we will transmit the contents of that email and your email address to the recip­i­ents.
  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the infor­ma­tion.
  * With your consent.

We may also disclose your personal infor­ma­tion:

  * To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any govern­ment or regu­la­tory request.
  * To enforce or apply our [Terms of Use](https://www.schellgames.com/schell-games-terms-of-use) and other agree­ments
  * If we believe disclo­sure is necessary or appro­priate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Schell Games, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging infor­ma­tion with other companies and orga­ni­za­tions for the purposes of fraud protec­tion and credit risk reduction.

### Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Infor­ma­tion

You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inac­ces­sible or not function properly.

If you do not wish to have your email address/​contact infor­ma­tion used by the Company to promote our own products or services, you can opt-out by checking the relevant box located on the form on which we collect your data or at any other time by sending us an email stating your request to [legal@schellgames.com](mailto:sglegal@schellgames.com).

### Accessing and Correcting Your Infor­ma­tion

You can review and change your personal infor­ma­tion by sending us an email at [legal@schellgames.com](mailto:sglegal@schellgames.com). Specif­i­cally, you can send us an email to request access to, correct or delete any personal infor­ma­tion that you have provided to us. We may not accom­mo­date a request to change infor­ma­tion if we believe the change would violate any law or legal require­ment or cause the infor­ma­tion to be incorrect.

### Data Security

We are committed to ​“Privacy by Design” concepts, and we have imple­mented measures designed to secure your personal infor­ma­tion from acci­dental loss and from unau­tho­rized access, use, alter­ation, and disclo­sure. All infor­ma­tion you provide to us is stored on our secure servers behind firewalls.

Unfor­tu­nately, the trans­mis­sion of infor­ma­tion via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal infor­ma­tion, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal infor­ma­tion trans­mitted to our Websites. Any trans­mis­sion of personal infor­ma­tion is at your own risk. We are not respon­sible for circum­ven­tion of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Websites.

### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

We may revise this Privacy Policy, for example, to reflect changes in the law, our practices, or features of our products. It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page with a notice that the privacy policy has been updated on the Website home page. These changes will be effective imme­di­ately upon posting. As a result, you should peri­od­i­cally review the Privacy Policy so that you are up to date on our most current policies and practices. The date the privacy policy was last revised is iden­ti­fied at the top of the page.

By using our Websites you agree to the terms and condi­tions of this Privacy Policy, and, by contin­uing to use our Websites after changes have been made, you agree to the changes.

### Still Have Questions?

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Policy, please contact us at:

Schell Games   
220 W. Station Square Drive  
Pitts­burgh, PA 15219
